

PHD STUDENT · SOFTWARE ENGINEER

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

□ (415)203-8543 | ☑ chi45@purdue.edu | ♠ hyung-gun.me | □ stnoah1 | ♠ hyung-gun | ➢ Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests_

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning and Temporal Action Anaylsis. In this area, I apply Machine/Deep Learning algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

Education

Purdue University

West Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT

· Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Yonsei University

Seoul, South Korea

• Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

• 2011-2013, 2-year military service

Skills_

Language Python, Matlab, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Machine/Deep Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras

Web Programming MYSQL/mongoDB, Flask/Node.js

CAD Tool Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, AutoCAD

ETC GAZEBO, ROS

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C2] H. G. Chi, S. Kim, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and Karthik Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020, accepted.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. G. Chi, and Karthik Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020, accepted.

Journal Papers

- [J3] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In *Computer-Aided Design*, 2020, accepted.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, **H. G. Chi**, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer*, pp. 1-15, 2019
- [J1] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)*, 33(3), pp. 1333-1339, 2019

Patents

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. Computer Input Automation System. KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

Research Projects

One-Shot Weakly-Supervised Learning for Temporal Action Localization

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Mar. 2020 - Present

- Propose a novel architecture to segment temporal boundaries of action in untrimmed videos with single training data for each class.
- Redefine action localization problem as a Reinforcement Learning (RL) problem and design the RL pipeline to improve the performance.

A Large-scale Mechanical Component Benchmark Dataset [C2]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Feb. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Introduce large-scale mechanical components a benchmark for the classification and retrieval tasks named Mechanical Components Benchmark.
- Develop a data collecting pipeline including annotation interface and database.
- Benchmark state-of-the-art 3D Deep Neural Networks for classification and retrieval tasks to explore the descriptor for mechanical components.

Hand segmentation with RGBD-T data [C1]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Jul. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Propose a novel hand dataset by fusing RGB-D and thermal data for hand segmentation.
- · Develop a method which segment hands and objects with a multi-modal Deep Neural network dealing with RGBD-T data.

Part Geometry Net (PGNet) [J3]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Oct. 2018 - Aug. 2019

- Build a Generative Adversarial Network which generates 3D objects given a discrete category condition and continuous instance-level attributes by fusing the various types of geometric information.
- Introduce a part identifier module which learns part geometry to preserve part properties of 3D objects.

Latent Transformation Neural Network (LTNN) [J2]

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - April. 2019

- Develop a fully-convolutional conditional generative network which is capable of view synthesis using a light-weight neural network suited for real-time applications.
- Introduce the conditional transformation unit which is designed to learn the latent space transformations corresponding to specified target views.

Visual Programming Language for Mobile Robots and IoT Nodes

C-Design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

- Propose a web-based visual and spatial programming language that allows novice users and small industries to program mobile robots and IoT Nodes to execute planned tasks.
- Develop a virtual world using the Robotic Operating System (ROS) and GAZEBO which simulates the interaction between mobile robots and IoT devices.

Interpretable 3D Deep Neural Network [J1]

Knowledge-Based Design LAB, Yonsei Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Jul. 2017

- Propose an evaluation method for 3D Deep Neural Networks by visualizing the impact of each voxel of each 3D object.
- Develop a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network for demonstration.

Working Experience

Software Engineer and CEO

Seoul, South Korea

NEIL LAB CORPORATION

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

- Found and lead a start-up company as a CEO and Software Engineer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the SeongNam Industry Promotion Agency.
- · Develop an office automation system specifically for automating office tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts.
- Designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (*Relevant patent:* [P1])

Mechanic and Squad leader

Inje, South Korea

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

Apr. 2011 - Jan. 2013

- Maintain military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Lead a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.

Academic Activities

Reviewer The British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC) 2020.

References

Karthik Ramani Professor, Purdue University **Soo-Hong Lee** Professor, Yonsei University

ramani@purdue.edu shlee@yonsei.ac.kr

AUGUST 12, 2020